Pablo Batis FRONT-END DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Smart Age Solutions | 02/2020 - Currently

Responsible for designing, building and optimizing the Magento platform interfaces. Development in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, PHP and React, producing the layout of the digital product and creating interactivity between the elements of the page or application. Thus, the professional is not part of a single team, but usually moves between the areas of design and back-end development.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER INTERN

UNISUAM(University) | 08/2018 - 02/2020

Responsible for programming the front of the web application, basically, the front-end developer is responsible for transforming the design created by the Web Designer into HTML and CSS code. The developer also works with programming languages, among the best known, highlighting the most traditional ones: Java, PHP, C#, C, C ++ and among others.

DATABASE CONSULTANT

Scientific initiation scholarship(Pibic - CNPq) | 05/2019 - 02/2020

I am one of the founders of the SOD System, a project within UNISUAM that is the creation of a data optimization system, where the main focus is to create an ERP system that collects data from the institution's practice centers and in the end occurs modeling them. He worked directly with MySQL / SQL, Google Data Studio and PowerBI.

EDUCATION

UNISUAM

Bachelor of Computer Science - 2017 - 2021

SFNAC

Computer Technician - 2015 - 2016

SFNAI

Graphic Design - 2014 - 2015

English Course - MET Certification (Michigan English Test), 2013 - 2016

Web Designer, 2013 - 2016

About Me

Hello, my name is Pablo Batista, I currently work as a front-end developer. During these learning cycles, I had the experience of progressing some knowledge that is extremely important for my career, and all this knowledge is connected and gives me knowledge within the area of UX to UI, they are: PHP; HTML / CSS; C / C ++; Vue.js; Laravel; Angular 7; Wordpress; Magento; Database, Heuristic Analysis; Benchmarking; Creation of visual identities; Branding and others. These lessons learned have given me greater mastery of technology, marketing and design.

Contact

- 🔀 pablohrbatista@gmail.com
- 📞 +55 (21) 99551-1201
- (in /in/pablo-batista-16a7a7180/
- behance.net/pabrul
- github.com/pabrul

Skills



































